dottech.org 2013-11-04

# Privacy Statement | Reviews, news, tips, and tricks | dotTech

Just like any other website on the internet, we run statistical plugins on dotTech.org to keep track of website statistics. These plugins track things like what is the most popular post, how many people visited dotTech on a certain day, how many people downloaded a certain software, etc. Any information collected by these statistical information is strictly on how users interact with dotTech.org. All data is only used for analysis to improve dotTech.org (e.g. figure out which topics people are interested in). Information is never sold, traded, given away, or other undesirable acts. If you would like to know exactly what information these statistical plugins are collecting you can check them out for yourself: [Top 10](http://wordpress.org/extend/plugins/top-10/) and [Google Analytics](https://www.google.com/analytics/).

That being said, WE DO NOT WANT ANY OF YOUR PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION. Outside of the statistical usage mentioned above, ANY PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION (such as name, e-mail address, and IP address) SENT TO US IS ON YOUR OWN ACCORD, SUCH AS WHEN YOU E-MAIL US, POST A COMMENT, MAKE A FORUM POST, SIGNUP FOR EMAIL NOTIFICATIONS, OR REGISTER ON DOTTECH.ORG. HOWEVER DO NOT WORRY. WE DO NOT CARE FOR YOUR INFORMATION AND WE DO NOTHING WITH IT (WE DO NOT SALE, TRADE, GIVEAWAY, OR DO OTHER BAD AND MEAN THINGS) EXCEPT TO SEND YOU AN E-MAIL IF NEEDED (THIS E-MAIL WILL NOT BE SPAM) OR A SIMILAR KIND GESTURE; also if the situation demands it, your IP may be compared to that of others to determine if you are a spammer or a repeat offender under a different name. IF YOU DO NOT FEEL COMFORTABLE GIVING OUT YOUR REAL NAME AND E-MAIL ADDRESS THEN DON’T. WE DON’T CARE. The Internet was not designed to be a private place. IF PRIVACY IS A BIG ISSUE, USE A PROXY, OR OTHER TECHNIQUES, TO HIDE YOUR IP ADDRESS WHENEVER YOU SURF THE INTERNET. Just be careful because many proxies are not anonymous and can in fact hurt you, in terms of privacy and collecting your personal information, more than not using a proxy. To learn more about what an IP address is, read [Wikipedia](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ip_address).

Lastly, to earn some revenue to support the efforts of dotTech.org, We run ads. One of our major ad platforms is Google AdSense ads. Google, and Google’s advertising partners, use special tricks to make sure they are doing good advertising. Here is the official legal blurb:

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

What Google does is out of my control. Sue them if you don’t like it.

By using dotTech.org we assume you accept everything mentioned here. If you don’t, leave now. We hate to see you go. =(

 _P.S. Please don’t sue us. We don’t have an army of lawyers nor can we afford any._
